Finding Aid for Constance E. Cumbey papers, 1920-2004
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Other Media
  - VHS Tapes
    - Cumbey-Presentation on Pat Robertson: "Who is this Man? Let's Piece the Clues Together," 1988, 1 videotapes VHS (TM), master (Box 85)
      (tape no. 18)
    - "Fetal Tissue Research:The Untold Story"; a Life Issues Television Production, 1 videotapes VHS (TM) 30 minutes (Box 85)
      (tape no. 19)
    - Interview with Cumbey on Mother Angelica Live TV Program 05/17/1988, 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 85)
      (tape no. 20)
    - Michigan Alliance of Families-New Age Conference II, Cumbey discussion of the New Age, 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 85)
      (tape no. 21)
    - PBS Special, "Voices of a New Age," 1994, 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 85)
      (tape no. 22)
    - The 700 Club television program February 28, 1989-March 2, 1989, 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 85)
      (includes program on New Age Movement featuring former New Age leader)
      (tape no. 23)
    - "Viewpoint on the News: The New Age Debate", 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 85)
      (tape no. 24)
    - Kathy Walsh television interview of Cumbey on TV2 1/24/1994, 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 85)
      (tape no. 25)
    - Armageddon Script, Cumbey, 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 85)
      (tape no. 26)
  - Cassette Audio Tapes
    - Constance Cumbey
      - Constance Cumbey, #5-8, 2 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        (tape no. 1-2)
      - Constance Cumbey The New Age Pts. 1 and 2, 2 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        (tape no. 3-4)
      - Constance Cumbey Series 1, 1-7, 2 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        (tape no. 5-6)
      - Constance Cumbey, Series 2, 1-4, 8, 2 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        (tape no. 7-8)
      - Cumbey, 1-5, 5 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        (tape no. 9-13)
      - The New Age Movement
        - Introduction, 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        - "Inspiration" vs. Channeling, 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        - Doctrine of "Chrystology", 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        - Doctrine of the "Godhead", 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        - Doctrine of "Atonement" vs. "Reincarnation", 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        - The "Apostasy", 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
    - Firefighters For Christ, Culver City, CA.
      - A Planned Deception #1, Constance Cumbey, 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
    - Huntington House Tapes
      - The Hidden Dangers of the Rainbow. Is The Antichrist In The World Today? Is "Lord" Maitreya The Antichrist? By Constance Cumbey, 4 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        (tape no. 21-24)
    - Law Talk, WMUZ Detroit
      - 1991, 2 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        (tape no. 25-26)
      - 1993 David Whitaker, 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        (tape no. 27)
      - 1993 Outcome Based Education, 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        (tape no. 28)
      - 1993 America 2000 Cathy and Greg Finnegan, 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        (tape no. 29)
      - 1993 Constitutional Convention, Chip Bishop, Rick Butkowski, 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        (tape no. 30)
      - 1993 Curtis Rundell, 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        (tape no. 31)
      - 1993 Criminal Justice System, Stephen Markman, 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        (tape no. 32)
      - 1993 Tort Litigations, Harry Philo, 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        (tape no. 33)
      - 1993 Health Care Law, Dr. James Bridges, 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        (tape no. 34)
      - 1993 District Courts, William Bledsoe, 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        (tape no. 35)
      - 1993 Father Paul Marx, 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        (tape no. 36)
      - 1993 Home Schooling, Alan Cropsey, 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        (tape no. 37)
      - 1993 David Katz, 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        (tape no. 38)
      - 1993 Norm Hughes, 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        (tape no. 39)
      - 1994 James Miller, 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        (tape no. 41)
      - 1994 Jim Parks, 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        (tape no. 42)
      - 1994 Michelle Miller, 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        (tape no. 43)
      - 1994 Eileen Brown, 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        (tape no. 44)
      - 1994 New Year's Eve, 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        (tape no. 45)
      - 1994 Jim Miller, Last Show Before Election Primary, 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        (tape no. 46)
      - 1994, 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        (tape no. 47)
      - 1995, 5 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        (tape no. 48-52)
      - 1996 Malachi Martin, 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        (tape no. 53)
      - 1996 Barry Waldner, 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        (tape no. 54)
      - 1996, 3 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        (tape no. 55-57)
      - 1997 Christian Coalition, 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        (tape no. 58)
      - 1997 Mike Betzold, 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        (tape no. 59)
      - 1997 David Newman, 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        (tape no. 60)
      - 1997 New Age Dorothy, 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        (tape no. 61)
      - 1997, 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        (tape no. 62)
      - 1998, 3 audiocassettes (Box 86)
        (tape no. 63-65)
      - 1998, 2 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 66-67
      - 1999 Javier Solana, 1 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 68)
      - 1999, 4 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 69-72)
      - 2000 Joan Ueon, 1 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 73)
      - 2000, 4 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 74-77)
      - 2001 Larry Wasser, 1 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 78)
      - 2001 Cliff Kincaid, 1 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 79)
      - 2001 Soap Box, 1 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 80)
      - 2001, 2 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 81-82)
      - 2002 David Lee, 1 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 83)
      - 2002 Herb Peters, 1 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 84)
      - 2002 "Open Lines", 1 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 85)
      - 2002 Judge Callahan, Eric White, 1 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 86)
      - 2002 Dan Manville, Prisons, 1 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 87)
      - 2002 Mary Jo Anderson, 1 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 88)
      - 2002 Faith Towler (Box 87)
        (tape no.89)
      - 2002 Cornerstone Magazine (Box 87)
        (tape no.90)
      - 2002 Suzanne George, Dr. Migliozano, 1 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 91)
      - 2002 Microchip, 1 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 92)
      - 2002 Herb Peters, Javier Solana, 1 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 93)
      - 2002 Schools, 1 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 94)
      - 2003 Rev. Moon, 1 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 95)
      - 2003, 4 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 96-99)
      - 2004, 2 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 100-101)
      - Undated, Judge Kelly, Mark Buche, 1 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 102)
      - Undated, Home Invasion Killing, Javier Solana, 1 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 103)
      - Undated, Dr. Byrne, 1 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 104)
      - Undated, Father Paul Marx, Gino Vitale, 1 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 105)
      - Undated, Peter Dugan, 1 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 106)
      - Undated, Gary Allward, 1 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 107)
      - Undated, Jim Hirsu, 1 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 108)
      - Undated, Demond Wilson, 1 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 109)
    - Eustace Mullins
      - The Big Lie Technique of Constance Cumbey 1986, 1 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 110)
    - Pointe Publishing, Insights on the New World Order 1981-1990
      - 1987 New Age Debate: Constance Cumbey vs. Christian Mystic Elizabeth Burroughs -- Seattle Center, WA., 2 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 111-112)
      - 1987 Constance Cumbey on Trinity Broadcasting (TBN), 1988 Constance Cumbey -- The New World Order and the Russian Connection, 1 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 114)
      - 1990 Interview: Constance Cumbey -- Earth Day 1990 WJR 1991 Constance Cumbey's New Age Monitor, 1 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 116)
      - Undated, A Planned Deception, Constance Cumbey Radio Interview, Southwest Radio Church, 2 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 117-118)
      - Undated, Apostasy in the Church: the New Age Christ, Constance Cumbey, 2 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 119-120)
      - Undated, Constance Cumbey vs. MAFU and Dr. Marcel Vogel. Christians, Crystals, and Computers, Seattle, WA., 2 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 121-122)
      - Undated, Melanin and the Mark of the Beast, Constance Cumbey, 1 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 123)
      - Undated, Nazism and the New Age, Constance Cumbey (Box 87)
        (tape no.124)
      - Undated, Prophecy Seminar, Tulsa, OK. Host, John Barela, 1 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 125)
    - National Religious Broadcasters
      - 1986 Broadcaster's Luncheon, Constance Cumbey, 1 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 126)
    - Something Beautiful
      - Parts 1-5, 5 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 127-131)
    - Southwest Radio Church
      - Constance Cumbey, The New Age Movement, 2 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 132-133)
      - The New Age Movement, The New Age Movement in Prophecy Part I, 1 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 134)
      - The New Age Movement in Prophecy Part II, Nazism and The New Age Movement, 1 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 135)
      - The New Age Clean Up, 1 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 136)
      - A Planned Deception, 2 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 137-138)
    - United Methodist Holy Spirit Conference, Flint, MI.
      - Atty. Constance Cumbey, Address #2, 1 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 139)
      - Atty. Constance Cumbey, Address #4, 1 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 140)
      - Atty. Constance Cumbey, Address #6, 1 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 141)
      - Constance Cumbey Workshop, 1 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 142)
    - Jack Kevorkian
      - 1993, 3 audiocassettes (Box 87)
        (tape no. 143-145)